# SIMON MOR

Phone: +972 54 205 5028 Email: simomor@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/simonmor/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/simonmor/</a>

Github: <a href="https://github.com/MagusM">https://github.com/MagusM</a>



## **Professional Summary**

Very-qualified and motivated technology team leader & full Stack Developer, familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages backend and frontend.

Experienced and building a team and taking handling project from early stages.

I am handling any part of the process with ease. I am a team player with excellent technical abilities and proven project leader.

#### My Accomplishments

Self-taught accomplished software developer.

Held ownership over products of different scopes and sizes and multiple.

Driven leader managing to build and unite teams of various sizes and taking control of project in different sizes and accelerate development and achieving road maps goals.

## **Software Languages**

React, NodeJS, VueJS: Expert Level
Docker: Intermediate Level
AWS: Intermediate Level
Linux/Unix: Advanced lev
PHP: Expert Level
Git: Expert Level
SQL: Expert Level

Liliax, Ollix. Advanced le

ام

## **Work Experience**

TEAM LEADER WEB DEVELOPMENT - MatrixBI - Herzliya, ISRAEL - January 2021 - August 2021

Team leader - web team | NodeJS, React, TypeScript, Postgres, Azure

- Leading the development of the national application of epidemiology investigation used by Israel government and Health department
- Uniting a team, taking control and ownership over a startup like project.
- Building working methods with the team, implementing Agile and sprints.
- Help defining project vision, short and long goals.
- Leading the team and the project increasing the quality of the service. Bringing the application to be ready for even shelf product within months.
- Developing with Nodejs, React, TypeScript.

## TEAM LEADER WEB DEVELOPMENT- Incredibuild - Tel Aviv, ISRAEL - Aug 2019 - January 2021

#### Team leader & technology leader - web team | PHP, Laravel, NodeJS, React, Wordpress

- Leading the technology development of the entire company site and store.
- Ownership of the company site and store.
- Led the redesigning process of the company on the technology side.
- Managing agile, tasks and priorities in the team on production deployment processes.
- Acting as a devops to the site and store.
- Head of training.

#### FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER- Wobi LTD - Tel Aviv, ISRAEL - December 2017 - August 2019

# Full Stack Web developer & Project leader in Car & services team | PHP, Laravel, Jquery, NodeJs, React

- Building company main product server & client side to support the on-going demand of clients activities.
- Turning an outdated unscalable code to modern app architecture using Laravel framework.
- Refactoring and building new system with better clean code focusing on performance to give results faster on demand.
- Integration Salesforce system as a CRM layer and refactoring the system services to work with it.
- Designing new services and features to serve all important clients within company.
- Training another team.

#### SERVER DEVELOPER -Walla! News - Tel Aviv, ISRAEL - July 2016 - December 2017

#### Backend developer in Mail & Services Team

I have led and developed the Mail Application with constantly releasing new features and functionalities.

- Engineering configuration server in PHP to provide best mail service.
- Building and Maintaining Open Source API and in house "CASTLE" framework implementation
- Implementing IMAP server by protocol

• In charge of data migration to CLOUD using Amazon Web Services.

SERVER DEVELOPER – Wiser – TLV-San Francisco, US – August 2015 - July 2016

# Backend developer in Legacy Team | PHP Yii framework

- In charge to maintain the legacy system.
- Building application new features.

# **Education**

- FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT WITH REACT & NODE COURSE Coursera & Hong Kong Uni 2019
- BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, CHEMICAL ENGINEERING –SCE collage of Engineering Ashdod, ISRAEL 2007-2013